# HANNA TISCHER

hannalethtischer@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/hanna-leth-tischer

hannalt.github.io

704-928-7887

About

Hanna Tischer is a thoughtful, ambitious, and creative Tech Specialist with professional

Leadership Experience. Her technical skills are backed by her unique ability to communicate them.

This allows her to continually lead teams to out-perform their goals.

Education

## University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill

Expected May 2022

Bachelor of Science (B.S.) in Computer Science

Bachelor of Arts (B.A.) in English, concentration in Creative Writing

GPA: 3.681

Honors

**Honors Carolina** - Highly competitive, four-year academic program enrolling 10% of each class **Buckley Public Service Scholar** - Four-year fellowship focused on community service **UNC Dean's List** - Spring 2019, Fall 2019, Qualified - Spring 2020, Fall 2020, Spring 2021

Professional Experience

#### **General Electric Gas Power**

Atlanta, GA

rience Digital Technology Intern

May 2021 - August 2021

- Used Tableau to create Operations Dashboards to standardize the definition of application operations success across GE Gas Power.
- Created an automatic Natural Language Processing (NLP) classifier for application incidents, changes, and requests which increased the efficiency of ticket and application problem identification.
- Created an Automatic Application Verifier to on-demand and quickly check the web statuses of critical apps during vulnerable events.
- Worked with a GE Global Research Center Team to use a Zero-Shot BART Model to make a binary decision on information requests.

#### **Department of Computer Science, UNC**

Chapel Hill, NC

Research Assistant (RA)

August 2020 – Present

- Used NLP models to research for sustainability and social good applications.
- Integrated knowledge graphs with social media datasets to be used in the training of models.
- Lead and participated in a weekly undergraduate reading group focusing on current Computer Science Research.

#### **Department of Computer Science, UNC**

Chapel Hill, NC

Teaching Assistant (TA)

January 2020 – Present

- Organized a team of twelve other Teaching Assistants to create curriculum for the class.
- Conducted the selection and onboarding of new TAs.
- Held classes and office hours for ~200 students each semester.
- Graded homework, programming assignments, exams, and hardware labs.

### Ruffalo Noel Levitz, LLC at the UNC Engagement Center

Chapel Hill, NC

Shift Supervisor, former Development Representative

January 2019 – August 2020

- Oversaw the collection of approximately \$1M worth of donations while managing a team of ~25 employees.
- As a Development Representative, raised \$50,000 by calling UNC alumni and parents.
- Actively recruited, interviewed, and trained team members.

Skills

Language Skills: Spanish (Intermediate), Danish (Basic)

**Computer Skills:** Java, C/C++, Python, Html/CSS, TypeScript, Swift, Git/GitHub, Linux/Unix, Vim, MatLab, Microsoft Office Suites, Tableau Desktop, Tableau Server